Hunger and Ukka
Hi, I'm Mr. Hanger, born and raised in the Crab Room at Starlust.
I'm Mr. Hanger, born and raised in the Crab Room at Starlust.
Thank you very much.
Let's have a quick word with today's guest.
This is our idol.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Director Murahoshi of Ukka and this is Yukirinu.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, um, Mr. Yuki, this is your first participation this time.
Thank you very much.
My name is Mr. Hanger,
Please feel free to talk with me,
I would like you to feel free to talk with me and sometimes touch my hanger,
I would like to ask you to touch my hanger from time to time and play with me,
Do you have any recent events?
Yes, I do.
What was it?
In August, there were many summer events,
I had a lot of fun performing at various events.
I also went to Okinawa and Osaka.
I also went to Osaka.
I went to a lot of places.
Do you have any memories?
But it was the first time in a long time that I could go to Osaka,
And, you know..,
Event?
I had done an event in Fukuoka before, and now I was going to do it in Osaka,
I was able to find a different atmosphere.
Also, there were a lot of songs that I hadn't played in a while.
I thought that was fun.
It was fun.
No, it's nice.
But I wish you could go to Okinawa, too, Hanger.
You've never been?
No, Mr. Hunger.
No?
I think there are many fans in Okinawa,
If you do, I would appreciate it if you could tell your fans in Tokyo to come to Okinawa.
Thank you very much.
Now then, here we are,
I would like to ask you to announce the three major group-starting competitions,
May I make the announcement?
Okay, I will.
Yes!
Fangert and Ulka!
Then I will make an announcement.
Here is my bread!
Yes!
May I read them out?
1. noodles, 2. red blue, 3. tuna mayo onigiri!
I see.
1 is Noodle, 2 is Red Blue, and 3 is Tuna Mayo Onigiri... 1 is Noodle, 2 is Red Blue, and 3 is Tuna Mayo Onigiri... all food!
Yes, I was called?
They are so crispy. May I start with Noodle No. 1?
Yes, I often say that noodles are my favorite food,
Karaage Ramen, hamburgers,
Yes, that's right.
I love ramen among those foods.
You love ramen, don't you?
I really love ramen,
But actually, I really like noodles,
Really? Even soba noodles and rice bowls?
I also love chilled Chinese noodles,
All of them.
I've recently learned to eat somen noodles.
You can eat it now?
I used to eat it, but not so much that I couldn't eat it.
I used to eat it.
With ginger.
It's so good!
So you're going to eat it with ginger from the beginning, not with mentsuyu?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not in the ginger.
That's right.
But I still want to eat somen noodles.
I see.
I'd like to know more about it.
By Mr. Yuki.
Yes.
So if it wasn't for the noodles.
I wouldn't be here now.
LOL.
I'm not here now.
I'm not here.
That's how long I've been gone.
That's all.
I play an important role.
It's me.
Thank you, Mr. Nationwide.
Thank you very much.
Only men can win.
Okay, Red Bull 2, what's this?
Yes, this Red Bull is pretty much always one of my favorite drinks.
I guess so. I drink it a lot,
I bought a box of it when I bounced one time,
I bought a box.
When my mom talked about it like I have het moto,
She said, "You have a lot of single bottles and stuff.
Then she bought me a box.
She's so kind.
I had a bit of a bounce once,
I also bought a box of peaches recently. But I don't think I've been so heavy lately,
I'm getting really heavy.
Yes, it's a mess, about four times a week, Presley.
But if I drink it every day, it doesn't break me out too much.
Is that part of it?
My blood is like Red Bull.
Red Bull has the same nutrients.
Well, that's the point,
I have never had Red Bull,
When would you recommend drinking it?
I see.
Red Blue is usually taken when you really shouldn't sleep.
There are times when you shouldn't sleep.
But you know what?
When you are tired.
Ah! When you're tired.
Yes, but I like it.
But neither Murahashi nor I have ever had it.
What?
You've never had it either?
I've never had it.
What? ! You drink half the water of a lifetime.
I see.
I've never had a Red Joule either.
Oh, why?
Oh, but I see.
Chassis, you know, like drinking it.
I guess so. I don't drink much.
I see. I see.
You're just like me.
That's right. We are the same,
That's why I drink when I'm tired.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, when I went home after the concert,
I feel a little tired today.
I drink when I'm tired,
Oh, I see. Well, I'll take this as an opportunity to drink when I'm feeling a little tired, too. It's a good thing to drink when I'm tired, too. I see. Well, I'll take this as an opportunity to drink when I'm a little tired, too.
Now, let's look at the third and final item, the tuna mayo onigiri.
May I have this?
This is, you know, Rinu and I...
That's right.
What's the other one called?
Another bonding one.
Yes, it really is.
And the fact that we're doing onigiri.
I've done it with this Matsuyama Onigiri.
Caleco, how many years ago?
8 years?
Like 8 or something.
I was a junior high school student, and he was a foreign exchange student going there.
That's right.
Were you hungry at the time of the match?
He would bring onigiri (rice balls).
That's when I met him.
That's him?
Yes, that's right. I met him at Onigiri before that.
What's it like? You are very excited?
I have been with a couple so far.
There is Shaki-san, whom Riri likes. There's Shaki, for example. I think there are people who like Rinu.
I think there are people like Shaki-san,
I was eating that, too,
But when I ate this,
What do you call it? Nostalgia?
It was as if I wanted to be with them from the beginning.
I was already fluttering with nostalgia.
It filled a hole in my heart.
It was like...
Then it's really in my life already.
I really don't know if I want to be with you anymore.
A lot.
I've been affected by it.
On Shu?
You're such a leader.
I love salmon in nigiri too.
You're so sweet.
I'm going home.
I don't know...
I like other things too.
Like okaka (bonito flakes).
Of course.
I like Matsuyama too, and I like all of them. Of course I like all of them,
I like all of them, but in the end, what I come back to is..,
Mori-no-Atatunamaya Onigiri, I would call them Shaki Onigiri.
Yes, that's right.
It's a little bit like a hometown.
Yes, it is. I've had it before.
Probably.
I sometimes make a face like that,
I don't eat it. I don't eat it at all.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm serious.
I wonder what it is.
I'd like to eat onigiri, too.
I'd like to eat some onigiri.
I recommend onigiri.
Oh, will you ask me a good question?
I'd like to ask you what I like best in this restaurant.
The one I like best is
Lawson's onigiri.
Oh, Lawson's
is the most delicious onigiri-n onions. Oh, it's Lawson. is the most delicious.
What's the difference?
Well, I don't know, it's just my personal opinion, but personally, I think it's the saltiness.
Salty!
Salty! Salty!
It's like the taste just comes right in.
It's a little bit salty.
I like it a lot.
I see. I'll take this as an opportunity, Mr. Lawson...
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Who?
Not Lawson-kun, not Shuki Onigiri, even though he's half-face,
If you're going to eat tuna mayo onigiri, why don't you try Lawson's onigiri?
Why don't you try it?
Hunger and Ukka!
Yes, I've heard a lot about you all, but today is the first time for me to introduce hangers and vodka,
How was your first time performing at Hunger and Ukka today?
Well, I was really nervous. It was the first time for me to meet Hangar-kun.
Well, he also saw my temporary performance.
He is a big fan?
Really?
It was his third time.
He gave me great feedback, and I was glad.
If you had seen it for the second time, you would have seen it for the second time, wouldn't you?
No, I thought it was probably too late for them to get the message.
It got through to Haga-kun.
It's terrible, and you've already dressed up today.
I was totally dressed up.
You spiked your hair.
And your hair too.
Yes, I did.
But it was fun.
It was good.
Thank you all.
So, finally, can I take a look back from Haga-kun?
Yes, I do.
I will continue to appear at various major events and live performances,
Please check the official website and Twitter for more information.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, I am Hanger-kun,
I would like to ask you to give a message to the camera while hanging onto the hanger.
May I?
Yes, I understand.
You guys, finally, you are going to the hanger!
I'm going!
Let's go!
Are you getting this?
No, wait a minute.
It's a little big, Mr. Hanger. You're surprisingly comfortable, Mr. Hanger.
Oh, it's good, isn't it?
Okay, last message.
Please leave a message.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
It was a very enjoyable episode.
Thank you very much for watching!
Please enjoy the meal.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Yacchan
Fukuchan
I sent this message courtesy of